How are you, man?
Look, the form is great, it's very hard.
We just have some quotes to correct.
Here, if you look, for example, at the Azure Update in record 11,
I have almost all the data loaded.
Notice that here we have values, here we have values,
We have values ​​here, there.
Here, this is not being saved for me.
I would have to validate if it is something specific that has been left,
but, well, that's not up to you.
If you correct it, then you might get something extra,
it would be appreciated.
But no, don't worry about that part.
However, look, there is data here.
This one is not carrying me, nor is it saving me,
But anyway, that has nothing to do with you.
What else?
Here, look, all this is full, all this is full.
Here there is data.
There is also information here.
These are not being saved either.
I have to validate that.
These are not being saved either, but still,
It's something I have to validate.
These are also not being saved.
So, since they are not saved, obviously they are not loaded either.
or they are not loaded and are being saved.
That's something I figure out, don't worry about it.
But the point is, and here too, this is failing me.
And this one.
Everything that is not full right now is because it is failing me.
However, if all this data is full
It's not loading everything here.
Here, for example, before and before familiar.
If I go to relatives.
Here is data.
Here's TB, yeah.
TB, I should check yes here.
Diabetes.
Diabetes here, it's yes, you should check yes here.
And if I check type 1 or type 2, it should bring it here.
Here I already have type 1 in family members.
In type 1 relatives.
Well, in type 1 relatives you really have nowhere to match.
But in type 1 personals, for example, it should fall here.
Which would be straight into yes, really.
If I check yes, I should check here.
Per se.
And it's not falling.
Yes frame type 2.
That is, checking yes would be the same as type 2.
They are little details that I took care of.
But if I mark type 2.
Well, it should fall here.
And with marking yes, personal.
I'm here on personals.
By checking yes, in diabetes, you can fall here.
This one must fall.
So, genital surgery or I don't know what.
Genitourinary surgery.
Look here.
It's marked like this and it's not here.
Here in gestures, you marked almost all of them, which is great.
But this opiate pregnancy has data.
Stopic pregnancy.
Look here.
It has data.
And it's not here.
Births.
It says 0.
But here you give birth.
Oh well, it's marked 0.
Alright.
I thought I marked 1.
So, end of previous pregnancy.
End of previous pregnancy.
Notice that it has data.
And he didn't put it here.
So, I didn't use it.
In fact, the opposite is being said here.
Look.
Here he set a barrier, gave a norm, I don't know what, etcetera, etcetera.
While here I really, well, really there I don't know where that data comes from.
Because look, barrier.
Previous failure method, conception.
So, above method failure.
Barrier is the one who is marked.
Look.
I update.
It is the one that is marked.
So, here he put a barrier, gave me, etc.
Planned pregnancy.
It is marked yes.
And here it is marked no.
So, here on vaccines.
In vaccines.
Where is?
Vaccine, vaccine, vaccines.
Vaccines.
So, no tetanus vaccine, right?
So, tetanus is no.
Perfect.
They are all no.
But here, TDAP is yes, prior to pregnancy.
That is, TDAP should check here.
It's not marking.
Influence too.
Influence is also marked here.
However, here it is marked where it is not.
Dates are not loading.
All these dates are not loading.
This value one is not being checked here.
And these values ​​one, two, one, two, two, one
They are not marking here.
And either way it's going to get involved.
You have to review it completely because really...
I'm going to free you a part
why, because I have really done a wonderful job.
But please review the complete form.
At least the data that should be there.
That's it.
I check it and there is no problem if you check it well,
If not, no problem.
But at least the one that is there, I need it to be reliable.
I need it to charge well.
If I save here, this value, this value, this value here
This is what has to be marked.
It's the same as this.
It's not allowing me to edit.
I assume something...
I validate that.
Don't worry about that.
But please validate me with the complete form.
And not in pieces.
Let me know anything.